{"data":[{"question":"It is a well idea to encourage your husband and children to learn to cook a few simple meals while you are away.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"well","b":"to encourage","c":"to learn","d":"meals","answer":"1","explain":"- Well-> good","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The invention of the electric telegraph gave birth of the communications industry.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"invention","b":"birth","c":"of","d":"communications","answer":"3","explain":"- Of-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"With increasing development and use of computer technology, there is a newly disease to worry about.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"With","b":"development","c":"use","d":"newly","answer":"4","explain":"- Newly-> new","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"In some countries in Europe, teachers are allowed giving children some homework only at weekends.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"in","b":"are","c":"giving","d":"homework","answer":"3","explain":"- Giving-> to give","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Five prisoners were injured when they attempted to escape in the prison last night.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"were","b":"when","c":"attempted","d":"in","answer":"4","explain":"- In-> from","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Is driving a car more dangerous than to fly in a modern plane?\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"driving","b":"dangerous","c":"than","d":"to fly","answer":"4","explain":"- To fly-> flying","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"I'd like to write applying for the post of accountant in your company.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to write","b":"applying","c":"of","d":"in","answer":"2","explain":"- Applying-> application","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"I have five years of experience like an accountant and can speak English fluently.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"experience","b":"like","c":"speak","d":"fluently","answer":"2","explain":"- Like-> as","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"I feel very happy to get your letter after so a long time.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"happy","b":"to get","c":"so","d":"time","answer":"3","explain":"- So-> such","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The driver asked the passengers not to get off the bus while it was moved.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"asked","b":"to get","c":"while","d":"moved","answer":"4","explain":"- Moved-> moving","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"}]}